♫ Snowing and blowing up bushels of fun. ♫
♫ Now the jingle hop has- ♫
♫ jingle bell, jingle bell jingle bell rock. ♫
♫ Jingle bells chime in jingle bell time. ♫
♫ Dancing and prancing in jingle bell square. ♫
♫ In the frosty air. ♫
♫ What a bright time it's the right time. ♫
♫ To rock the night away. ♫
♫ Jingle bell time is a swell time. ♫
♫ To go glidin' in a one-horse sleigh ♫
♫ Mix and a-mingle in the jinglin' feet. ♫
♫ That's the jingle bell rock ♫
♫ Jingle bells, jingle bells jingle all the way. ♫
♫ Oh, what fun it is to ride in a one-horse open sleigh. ♫
♫ Dashing through the snow. ♫
♫ In a one-horse open sleigh. ♫
♫ O'er the hills we go. ♫
♫ Laughing all the way ♫
♫ It's the most wonderful time of the year ♫
♫ With the kids jingle-balling. ♫
♫ And everyone telling you "be of good cheer". ♫
♫ It's the most wonderful time of the year ♫
Leanne?
Oh, my God!
Listen carefully.
Your wife has been taken.
At 4:30 P.M.,
you will go to the Vatashca Street parking garage.
There, an level 2 you will find a very special car.
You will know which one.
Steal it.
There are cameras installed on the inside and outside of this vehicle.
I'm watching every move you make.
Drive it to the tap of the city and I will contact you there.
It's been a long time since you've driven...
But you'll have to overcome your fear if you want to save her.
Your wife is very beautiful.
If you want her back, then you will follow my instructions precisely.
If you contact the police, or if you get caught...
She will die.
You've done very well so far, Mr. magma.
During the course of this night,
you will be given several tasks.
If you fail at  any...
You will never see your wife again.
How do you like the car?
Do you like it?
It's armored.
It was designed especially for you.
Is she alive?
The police will be looking for you.
If they catch you,  ever...
The game's over. Is that clear?
Brent?
Why is this happening?
Please, help me. I'm so scared.
Where are you taking me? Where are you taking me? Wait!
She's fine.
For now.
She will remain that way as long as you follow my instructions.
I'm watching you, always.
Get rid of your phone.
What do you want?
Where are we?
No! Please, please, don't leave me here!
No!
Answer.
Speed up.
Faster.
Turn left.
Go through the intersection and turn hard left.
No, I can't do that. I'll dead end into the park.
Just do it.
It's Christmas.
There's gotta be hundreds of people in there.
I won't ask again.
Shit.
Came an!
Get out of my way.
Drive toward the market.
Smash into everything you can.
I can't do this!
You have no choice.
Jesus.
Excellent. Now drive onto the skating rink.
There's tan many people!
Now.
Get out of the way!
Go straight to the stage where the man is speaking. Knock it down.
-I'll kill him.     -Do it.
-Are you crazy?     -Now.
Now go down the stairs.
Ah, shit.
Ah...
Mr. magma, are you there?
Confirm you're still receiving.
I can hear you.
Where's my wife?
Keep going. Now.
Watch out, watch out!
Oh, no, no!
Jesus.
Bravo, Mr. Magna. Your first task is complete.
Am I done?
We're just getting started, my boy.
We're just getting started.
Turn right, now.
-The water truck.     -Yeah?
Smash into it!
Don't stop.
Speed up.
-Faster.     -The light's red down there.
Go through it.
Jesus.
Wonderful, Mr. Brent magma.
Now turn right. Pull into the underground construction zone.
Relax...
And you will await further instructions.
Get out.
-Get out, now!     -All right.
Do not get out of the car.
You heard me asshole, get out.
Now.
-Look, you got the wrong car. Walk away...     -Now!
-I'm doing you a favor.     -Get out.
-You don't wanna... walk away.     -Get out.
-You don't wanna steal...     -Get out of the car!
-Drive away.     -I can't! I got a kid in the car!
-Get out! What'?     -Drive away now!
-Drive.     -What do you want meta do with her?
Drive away! Take her with you! Do it. Drive!
All right, all right, all right!
Get off of me, asshole!
Do not ever point a gun at me, you hear me'?
Do not ever point a gun at anyone!
Unh! Don't ever touch me like that again. Do you know what I could have done to you?
The hell are you doing?
Strap yourself in.
-I'm not doing shit!     -Put on your seatbelt.
-No!     -Strap yourself in.
-Where are you going?     -Dust strap yourself in!
Kill her.
She has seen you and she has seen the vehicle.
I'm not gonna do it. I can't do that.
You either shoot her...
Or I'm going to shoot your wife.
One.
Two.
What? What? No.
I can't do that!
I'm not a killer.
It's the right choice. You'll need her.
You can keep the car.
Can I get out new?
I'll let you off right up here.     -She is not to be set free.
-L... listen.     -She is not to be set free.
-Understood?     -It's understand.
Oh, great.
Oh, my God.
What did you do?
Pull aver!
Oh! Shit!
On, God.
-What the hell are you doing?     -Put on your seatbelt!
Shit.
Hey, hey! Do not touch that gun, all right?
-I need bath hands to drive this car!     -Let go of me, asshole!
Do not touch that gun!
I don't care. I hope we crash. Help me!
This guy's trying to kill me!
What are you doing?
Pull us over!
Get in! Get inside the car!
-This guy's crazy! Help me!     -Get inside this car, all right?
You understand me? Stay in the car!
Pull aver.
Please slaw dawn.
-Oh, we're gonna die.     -Shut up.
Oh, my God.
Shit.
No, no, no.
You're the shittiest driver I've ever seen.
Back off, back off. Jesus!
On, shit!
Is he dead?
I hope not.
Listen to me, all right.
I have gotta get this car out of the city right now,
or they're gonna murder my wife.
-You understand me'?     -Sure.
Let me give you a ward to the wise.
Next time you wanna steal a car, try to make sure that no one is in it.
-It works better.     -I'm not stealing it, you asshole. This is my car.
What'?
You probably don't understand this...
"Because you're a criminal."
Things in this world belong to people before people like you take them.
This car, which was really great...
Till you added all these cameras to drain the battery...
Belongs to me. How'd you find the car'?
I got a call from a cap saying he saw my car parked in the garage where I found you.
What makes you think it was a cap?
Because he said so, genius.
What kind of cap calls to tell you he's got your car...
But he still leaves me inside of it?
-It wasn't the police that called.     -Then who was it?
I don't know.
-When was it stolen?     -Whenever you stale it.
When was the last time you saw it?
Two days ago, I guess. Look, you're obviously very disturbed.
Whatever trouble you're in, you deserve it.
Sc I'll cut you a deal. Pull aver and I'll let you walk away.
Or what, you shunt me?
Give me back my gun and I will.
What's a kid doing with a gun, huh?
Sc if some dipshit like you steps to me, I can take care of it.
That worked out well for you, didn't it?
Did you recognize the voice, huh, that voice?
-Your friend who wanted you to kill me'?     -He's not my friend, okay'?
I'm not the kind of person you wanna be caught kidnapping.
Yeah?
You special, is that it?
Just do me one favor, will you?
Shut the hell up.
You shut up!
What are you doing? Hey.
What the hell?
I can't believe you threw my phone out the window.
-I have a lot of money, you know.     -Good for you.
As in, if you let me go, I can give you a lot of money.
I don't want your money.
What do you want?
I want you to stop talking.
And I want my wife back.
-And he tank her?     -He did.
Whatever you awe him, I can get however much it is to pay him off, no problem.
We'll take care of it right now.
You have to let me go and stop almost killing us.
I would love to let you out of this car. Unfortunately, I can't do that.
Why the hell not?
Because he asked me not to and I am doing whatever he asks.
Se, what? What are you supposed to do?
I don't know.
Well, who is he?
-I don't know.     -What do you know?
Not much.
No, no, no!
Get up!
-Shut up.     -Ow! Aah!
Please. Please. Please, don't shunt me. Please, don't shunt me.
Quiet.
Answer.
It's time for your next task.
What is it?
More police are coming.
You'll have four minutes to getaway.
You'll follow my instructions exactly.
Someone wants to say hello.
Please, please.
Leanne?
Please. Help.
The clock starts now.
Damn it!
I'm totally screwed.
Oh!
-Ram him.     -What are you doing?
-Oh, my God.     -Keep going.
You're an idiot. That's assault with a deadly weapon.
They could shunt at us now.
-Speed up.     -Shit.
Turn right now.
Remember,
if they catch you...
You'll be a widower.
-Turn left.     -Oh, shit.
-Force him off the road.     -Look out!
-This is not very subtle!     -What are you talking about?
You're not making yourself very hard to find.
God, I promise I'll be good from new an. Please let me live.
-You're really not helping, okay'?     -Turn right.
Great.
Turn right down the alley.
Skip!
Holy shit.
-Two minutes.     -We're gonna die, please stop!
I don't think you'll make it.
What are you doing?
Take a deep breath, okay? And calm down.
Shit.
I wouldn't relax just yet.
-Shit.     -Not again.
-Did you think we were done?     -No, don't!
Goa!
You're running out of time.
Oh! Oh!
Tick tock, tick tock.
You have less than a minute.
-Turn into the park.     -No, not the park!
Here we go.
Your wife's time is running out.
Watch out! Unh!
Go through the intersection.
All right, hold an!
Not much time, Mr. magma.
Oh, no!
-No, please don't! Don't!     -Yep, yep, yep, hold on!
Five...
Four... Came an, came an, came an!
Three...
-...mo...     -Oh!
One...
Zero.
Bravo, Mr. Magna. Well done.
Bravo.
Your wife lives...
For now.
Well dune.
Answer.
"Brent Magna is both reckless and fearful."
"He is, in short..."
"...a dangerous driver and should pursue another profession."
Remember that review? It wasn't very flattering.
They're blind to your real talents...
Which are perfectly suited to my needs.
Do I know you?
I know you, Mr. magma...
-and I believe in you.     -Listen.
I need to know when this is all gonna be aver, all right? I need...
What are you doing?
Hey, what are you doing?
-I hate you.     -Yeah, I love you.
You realize I'll just have to buy another limited edition shelby super snake...
Take another six months to re-time the earns, open up the intake and customize it.
And then I'm gonna drive it aver your face.
-You sure know a lot about cars for...     -A girl'?
Yeah.
Wow.
I like fast cars and computers and bay things, haw butch.
It's the 21st century, you should join it.
-What are you doing?     -I'm documenting this shit.
I'm not going to jail after we get arrested.
-Well, nobody's gonna get caught, okay'?     -That's right, I forgot.
We're just gonna die...
"Because you're a dumb-ass who attacks the police with a damn car."
New every cap in this entire country...
Is hoping to put a couple bullets in our heads. Goad plan.
-We are alive.     -Barely.
Not much of a thinker are you?
Well, I didn't actually graduate from charm school like you...
So maybe someday you can give me some tutoring or something.
This is what he did to my beautiful, beautiful paint jab.
Just get in the car.
This is all the crap that he drilled into my carbon fiber interior.
This is the dumb-ass who got me into this mess.
-Stop filming me, all right'?     -Wave hi to the judge.
-Say hi to all your new friends in jail.     -Hey! Put that away! I'm trying... just stop it.
What is...? You're like add or something. What are you fiddling with new?
-Stop doing that.     -Why'?
Because this guy is watching us, okay?
-I need you to stop...     -I know what I'm doing.
-Dust listen to me for two seconds.      -I know what I'm doing.
See, I went to school and I know things...
Which is why I don't have to steal stuff, like some people.
If you're so smart, you tell me what's going on with all these cameras, huh?
They're all linked to a single feed.
It's not only encrypted, but it's piggybacking on a public server.
Huh?
It means they're hosting this live feed from these cameras...
An a government server without them knowing about it.
Sc anybody can watch it, even us.
-Wait a second.     -What?
-These aren't coming from the same place.     -Where are they coming from?
Lacks like a parking garage.
-Can you tell where it is?     -I don't know. Could be anywhere.
-Do you think it's where he might be'?     -Doubt it. But he can see it.
I don't like that he's watching us.
Do you think you can track him with that thing?
No, and if anyone did, he would just dump the ip address.
As long as his feed is hosted remotely, there's no way to find it.
-And that thing isn't really well-hidden.     -What?
Microphone.
-Oh, so he's listening to us too'?     -Probably.
Well, I'll give you this, you are bright.
It's called being educated.
You should look into it when you're not committing crimes.
Scratch that, you'll be in jail.
All right, answer.
Pull up power plant on the GPS.
We're kind of busy right now.
Learn to multitask.
Or let your new little friend help you. Lack under the visor.
Won't you do that?
I'm uploading a new set of directions.
That's the city power plant.
"At exactly 11:30."
You will be there.
Why are we going to the power plant?
Always so inquisitive.
I like it.
Listen carefully,
you're to break into the central roam.
Access the remote system...
-and insert that drive.     -What will that do?
You're a clever girl. I'm sure you'll figure it out.
He wants to cut the power off. Why do you want to cut the power?
You have some time until 11:30.
I wouldn't spend it trying to figure out my motives.
He's a real asshole.
So you don't know who that is?
No.
-No idea?     -I gut ideas.
People I used to work with...
But nobody I know could set up something like this.
So why you'?
Because I can drive.
-That's debatable.     -No, I mean, I used to race.
Really?
Really.
Professionally, like, real racing.
Don't think I ever saw you an TV.
There was a couple weeks there where you might have.
And?
And what?
I washed out.
How come'?
I don't know, I just did. Doesn't matter now.
That's a pretty shitty answer.
I washed out because I believed everybody who told me haw great I was.
Turns out the only thing I was great at was wrecking expensive cars.
Sc I fell off the pro circuit and I awed a bunch of money.
This is the only thing I was ever any good at...
So I took whatever job paid the most.
I did some things I'm not proud of.
But then I got out of it. And this...
Is why.
She's beautiful.
-Is she from here?     -Yeah.
She always wanted to came back, so we thought...
It'd be a good place to lay law and start aver.
Then I came home from work today, the dour is busted open...
The place is a wreck, there's bland on the floor.
My cell phone rings and this voice tells me...
if I ever wanna s...
If I ever wanna see her again...
I gotta do this jab.
And if I tell anyone, she'll be dead.
Next thing I know, I'm driving around in your car.
You souped this thing up yourself?
Yeah, it was a graduation present.
Nice. Something tells me your dad's not a mechanic.
He's the ceo of one of the largest banks in town.
We moved here about two years ago for him to take it over.
I barely see him,
but this car is the nicest gift he ever gave me.
Well, I'm sorry about all the damage.
You know, you could also apologize for taking me hostage.
You could apologize for putting a gun in my face.
I will if you let me out.
There's only one thing I'm concerned about right now...
And I'm gonna do whatever I have to to get her back.
Sc if he says you gotta stay in the car, you gotta stay in the car.
And where does that get you?
Why is this happening? What is he after?
You clearly haven't thought this through.
What happens when this is done and he gets what he wants?
Why would he even give her back to you?
If I were him, I'd kill her and I'd probably kill you.
Shit.
What?
I'd probably kill me tan.
Lacks like they've already been here.
If he was already here, why didn't he just take out the power himself?
I don't know.
Stop here.
Why?
Ever see what happens to a metal car...
When it touches a transformer that powers the whale city?
Dust wait here, I'll handle it.
What, alone?
Yeah, just be ready to go.
You sure?
Turn the car around, that's what I should do.
No, I should gain after her.
No, she's fine. She knows what she's doing.
Hello? I don't have much time.
I'm in this car with this man and his wife was kidnapped.
I speak English. Calm yourself.
Could you just send someone, please?
-What is your, uh, emergency?     -I don't know.
It's this voice telling us what to do. You have to help us.
-Exactly what is your location?     -I'm at the power plant.
-You make it so much fun.     -Shit.
Wherever that clever mind takes you, remember, I've already been there.
Look around.
You see? That's right.
The police will think you blew up the power station.
Can I give you some advice?
Run.
Come on, come on.
-Go, go, go!     -What, what, what?
-Drive, drive! Go!     -What happened?
Hold on. Shit.
Aah!
Faster!
Go faster!
Oh!
What are you doing? What are you doing?
I'm not dying for you.
-What happened?     -This is a part of his plan.
I was an camera that whale time.
He could have taken out the power himself, but he lured us in there...
"Because he wanted me to get caught an camera doing it."
You think the caps would ever believe me new?
Before, it was just you...
This car.
But new I'm screwed tan.
I'm sorry.
I gotta take care of myself.
Answer.
Stop her from leaving.
Go to hell.
Where are you taking me? Where are you taking me? Wait. Wait.
Leanne'? Leanne, can you hear me'?
Can you-f? Please.
Leanne, can you hear me?
Brent. Brent, what's going on?
Are you okay? Have they hurt you?
-Why is this happening?     -Leanne.
-Please help me! Brent?     -Leanne, are you all right, baby?
Please help me! I'm so scared.
I'm coming after you. I'm gonna make all this better.
-I'm gonna get...     -Aah!
What...?
Put my wife back an! Put her back an!
Is my wife all right?
I told you not to let her out of the car.
-I just need to see if she's...     -I warned you.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
I know what it's like to disappoint everyone, but I never thought that I'd let her dawn.
She's still alive.
You don't have to do this.
I want to.
What are you doing?
We gotta figure out his plan.
On, shit.
Get dawn, get dawn. Came an.
Okay, okay.
He was having you make this.
You're blocking off a path.
Half of these are one-way streets.
With these intersections blacked off, no one will be able to get through here.
Until they clean this mess up, there'll only be one way out of the city.
The rest will be a total shit show.
It's an escape route.
I just wish I knew what he was after.
You and me bath.
-Answer.     -I have good news for you.
This is your last assignment.
Look up number five in the GPS.
Follow the directions precisely. You have 10 minutes.
It's the bank.
What bank?
He wants us to rub my dad's bank.
Oh, shit.
We can't do that.
Do as instructed. The clock is ticking.
You can't. There's no way we could do that. The security's way tan tight.
Don't concern yourself with security.
-He wants us to get caught.     -Follow the GPS. Turn around.
This is a suicide mission. Listen, we can't do this.
Ignore her. Listen to me. Turn around now.
Am I gonna see my wife again?
Turn around.
I'm losing my patience with you.
Listen to me.
No.
I need to know when I'm going to see my wife.
No, turn the car around.
This is your last warning.
I need to be told that she is all right
and when this shit is gonna be aver!
Do you want to see her again?
Get control of yourself and turn the car around.
You can't do this.
-Listen to me, this is a setup.     -He will kill her.
That's why they used my car. It had to be me.
Think about it.
My dad, he cut off all of my funds.
New my car is causing havoc all aver the city...
And I'm seen rubbing his bank?
He wants us to get caught.
-What does he wanna steal?     -Money.
But that's just it, it's not that kind of bank.
What do you mean?
My dad runs an investment bank.
-There's no cash.     -Oh, shit!
-God.     -So, what, safety deposit boxes?
No, there's nothing like that in there, just computers.
-Bands. Bearer bands.     -Bearer bands? How old are you?
What is he after, then?
What's he trying to steal?
Unless...
Hold an!
Unless what?
Unless you don't want a record of your money.
-Right, right, like it's dirty money.     -Exactly.
-How do you move dirty money?     -Look out, look out!
-Came an, help me.     -They could encrypt the information...
An a numeric transfer key. A flash drive with account numbers.
If you stale one of these little transfer keys, right...?
-You could drain the accounts.     -Right.
No one would report that money stolen, it's not supposed to exist.
-Haw much are we talking about?     -It could be billions.
I should have been a banker.
Tell me that you're not serious.
Shit!
-I'm gonna go for it.     -No, don't go for it!
Here we go!
That was awesome.
Aah!
Aah! Get us out of here!
Watch out.
I really, really hate you.
I can understand that.
-What are you doing?     -Dust wait.
Okay, just sit still and be quiet for a minute.
Okay, it's dune. I bought us some time.
What?
I hacked into the server connected to these cameras, put an a loop of us driving.
-That's what he can see right now.     -Why?
Sc that you'll listen to me.
When we get there, we're gonna get caught and your wife will die.
We're his decays.
-Great.     -The powers out...
Which means the security infrastructure has been compromised.
And when that happens, there's a procedure.
Oh, shit.
My dad said something about this.
They're being moved. They're moving them right now.
They move anything sensitive to a secure location until the system is back up...
...and then they run a million tests.
By the time we get there...
We'll be rubbing an empty bank.
Please, let's just find a place to lack at it first.
I guarantee you it's swarming with caps.
How long do we have?
I don't know, five, maybe 10 minutes at the mast.
Watch where you're going, asshole!
I'll go check it.
Sc you were right?
I wish I wasn't.
Se, what do we do new?
I'm thinking.
You said there was a procedure. If the power goes out,
they'll move the drives?
Yeah.
Where do they move them?
I don't know, it's classified information for the bank.
Right. Shit.
But they gotta get picked up. They have to be picked up from here.
They've got all these caps here waiting for us.
I mean, what, is there a back door? Is there another entrance?
Remember that parking spat that we saw?
You asked if I thought that's where he was?
Yeah.
Well, I bet he's there now.
I told you you were bright.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Three, one,
nine, seven, two,
one, three, four,
two, six.
What?
Go, go, go!
-You got it'?     -Yeah, go!
Get them!
Answer me.
Answer me, answer me.
Answer!
Answer.
You're dead. Your wife is dead. It's over! Don't play with me!
We hold the cards new, asshole!
Could you be a little bit more careful?
How do I get this drive out?
Gut it!
Knack him! Hit him!
The voice speaks in german
Holy shit!
Oh. My God, go!
-Get down, get down, get down!     -Do something!
Please, get us out of here!
Oh!
Look out!
Hold on!
his is Sofia police department.
Shit!
Pull aver the car now!
Lose them.
Driver, pull aver car now!
We're trapped. Sit back. Hold an. You ready?
All right. Where's the gun? Where's the gun?
-Give me the gun!     -Keep your hands where we can see them.
New, just go with me on this, all right? Just go with me.
Back off!
Or I will shunt her head! I will blow her brains out!
Back off! Hey! Hey! See this?
Back off, or I'm killing this girl, you hear me?
I will kill this girl right now
What the hell are you doing?
I am going to blow her head off! Now, you. You. Yeah, you!
You okay? Hey!
Back, back, back! Or I'm killing this girl, you hear me?
Back off! Back off!
That's it, you're doing great.
Get out of my way, copper.
I can't believe that worked.
They're clear. I've sent you their location.
Intercept them.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna let you out.
What?
Came an. You're not a suspect anymore.
They think I kidnapped you. Tell them you were a hostage.
-No, I'm...     -I'm serious. I'm serious.
You've done more than enough for me.
I can't risk your life anymore.
-I really can't. You gotta get out, okay?     -No.
-Get out of the car.     -No.
Came an, get out of the car, will you?
I'm coming with you.
You're an extremely stubborn person, all right, you know that?
I know.
But I'm still not getting out of this car.
Besides, without me, you'd probably do something stupid, like get your face shat off.
All right.
You don't even know my name, do you?
No.
Aah! Go!
Damn it!
-Ow!     -Are you all right?
Hit him!
Damn it!
Get dawn, get dawn!
Dawn!
Lack out!
Oh, God.
Get us off the train!
-Where's the gun? Find the gun!     -I don't know!
-Find the gun!     -I'm lacking!
Find it!
-You got it'? Give it to me!     -I found it! Here!
Just hold the wheel for a second!
I need you to downshift! You ready?
Now!
I have an idea.
Get out.
Sc we meet up with him.
We do an exchange. The drive for your wife.
It'll never work. He'll kill us.
I have a way around it.
We use his camera to feed the video to the caps.
They'll see everything.
Answer the phone.
-Answer.     -You think you are so smart?
-I wouldn't be so...    -no, shut up and listen.
We have what you want, let's make a trade.
Where?
You know where I work?
I'll see you there in two hours.
Goodnight, asshole.
Where's my wife?
Where's my drive?
No. No! No!
Leanne!
Brent?
I need to know they're real.
You.
Fallow him.
Let her go first.
Oh, thank God you're here.
I love you.
I'm waiting.
Waiting.
Let's go.
Shoot them.
Brent, look out!
No! No!
-Throw her in!      -No! Aah!
-Are you all right?     -I'm okay.
Shit, they gut the kid.
-I gotta go after her.     -Go get her.
You stay with the police. Be careful.
Damn it!
Are you hurt, ma'am?
Shit.
He has a gun an me.
Brent, he has a gun.
Please hear me.
-I hope you can see this.     -sh
Quiet! Don't talk.
Brent, I'm trying to show you where we are.
Move out of my way!
Brent, yes!
-You're screwed, asshole!     -Shut up!
Come on, come on.
Oh!
Damn it!
What are you doing? Is that a camera?
Give it to me, give it to me! No, give it back!
Ah, shit! Bastard.
Damn it!
On, shit.
Shit.
The only way out of the city.
I know where she is.
-Pull aver! Give me the gun!     -What are you doing? Stop it!
You want us to die?
Brent'. Came an, came an!
-Get out!     -What?
Now!
Are you okay?
Are you okay? Yeah.
Stay there. You're under arrest.
Thanks.
Everybody back!
Ugh!
-I guess I owe you one, huh?     -And you owe me a new car.
Don't worry about the car. It just needs a new paint jab and she'll be fine.
-What's that?     -I don't know.
It's not mine.
-Hello'?     -Aren't you going to thank me?
I did for you what you could never do for yourself.
I showed you what you are made of.
Please  excuse me if I wasn't able to be there in person.
I'm sure you understand, under the circumstances...
It would have been most inconvenient for me.
If you're asking yourself who I am to you...
I am your greatest fan.
I always thought you could have been at the top of your profession...
If only you believed you could.
So that's it, you see.
Please send your lovely wife my best wishes for a happy Christmas.
I'm sincerely glad you worked things out to be with her for the holidays.
It's the season to be together with loved ones, so pm told.
I have very few loved ones.
My consolation is I have a lot of money.
And now, quite a lot more of it, thanks to you.
I doubt if our paths will cross again, but then, life is full of surprises.
So let's just say au
revoir.
Be assured,
it's been most entertaining.
死路十條
索非亞 保加利亞
道路封閉
警察局
來電
呼叫
加載外部設備
加載進度
死路十條
琳恩？
喔，天啊！
仔細聽好了
你的妻子在我們手上
下午四點半
到Vitasha停車場二樓
你會看到一輛很特別的車
你知道我什麼意思
搶過來
車裏有錄影鏡頭
我能看到你的一舉一動
開車到山頂，我會再跟你聯繫
我知道因為那次意外你很久沒有開車了…
但你必須克服你的恐懼，如果你還想救你的妻子
你的妻子很漂亮
如果你想她回到你身邊，那就按照我的指令行動
如果你打算報警，或者你被逮捕…
你就再也看不到她了
到目前為止你做的很好，麥格納先生
今晚的過程中
您將獲得各項任務
如果你失敗了…
你永遠不會再看到你的妻子
那輛車怎麼樣？
喜歡嗎？
改進了裝甲
是特別為你設計的
我妻子還活著嗎？
警察會一直追捕你
如果你被逮捕…
遊戲就結束，明白嗎？
布蘭特？
發生了什麼事？
求求你，救我，我怕極了
要去哪裡？要去哪裡？等等！
她沒事
至少現在沒事
只要你老老實實按我說的做
我會一直看著你的
把手機扔掉
你想要做什麼？
要帶我去哪裡？
不！求求你，放我出去！
不要！
我在
加速
再加速
左轉
穿過十字路口一直往前
不行，前面是個公園
按我說的做
今天是聖誕節
公園裏有很多人
我不是在徵求你的意見
媽的
閃開！
快閃開
去市場
你完全可以撞死他們
我不能！
你別無選擇的
天啊！
很好，現在去溜冰場
哇靠！那裏人更多！
快去
都給我閃開！
到舞台那裏，撞死那個演講的
-撞死他  -快去
-你就是個神經病？  -快去
現在衝下樓梯
喔，我靠
喔…
麥格納先生，還在嗎？
快回答
我還沒死
我的妻子在哪？
我們繼續  快！
小心，小心！
不，不，不！
天啊
布蘭特·麥格納先生，你的第一個任務完成了
是麼？
我們才剛開始
來我們繼續
右轉
-前面有輛飲料車  -喔？
撞過去！
別停
加速
-快！  -前面是紅燈！
闖過去
天啊
太漂亮了，布蘭特·麥格納先生
現在右轉，去地下停車場
放輕鬆…
等待下一步指示
滾出去
-滾出去，快！  -好了
別下車
沒聽到嗎？滾出去！快！
快！
-你上錯了車…  -快！
-我有一個建議  -快滾出去
-滾出去！  -快！
-你最好別搶這輛車…  -快滾出去！
-快開車  -靠！你沒看到這有個女孩嗎！
-滾出去！  -快開車！
-開車  -現在怎麼辦？！
把她帶上！快開車！快點！
好了，好了，好了！
把你的手拿開，你個混蛋！
不要再拿槍指著我！
也不要指著任何人！
你也不要再碰我！
什麼情況？你他媽在幹什麼？
繫好安全帶
-我才不繫！  -繫好安全帶
-就不繫！  -繫好安全帶
-你要去哪裏？  -繫好安全帶！
殺了她
她見過你，見過這輛車
不行，我做不到
殺了她…
或者我殺了你妻子
1…
2…
什麼？什麼？不
我不能殺了她！
我不是殺人犯！
明智的選擇，你還用得到她
你繼續在車裏呆著
我能下車嗎？
-為什麼？你害怕了嗎？  -她不能走
-聽…我說！  -她不能下車，明白嗎？
-明白了嗎？  -明白
非常好
天啊
你幹什麼？
靠邊！
我靠！
天啊
-你到底幹了什麼？  -繫好安全帶！
我靠
嘿！嘿！別碰槍？好嗎？
-我要兩隻手才能開車！  -放開我，混蛋！
不要再碰那把槍！
我才不管，你最好撞壞這輛車
救命！這個大叔要殺我！
你在犯什麼神經？
快讓車停下來！救命！
快回來！
-他想殺我！救命！  -快回來！好嗎？
給我老老實實呆在車裏！
靠邊
快減速
-我靠，我會死的  -閉嘴
天啊
我靠！
靠，靠，靠
你是我見過的最爛的車手
閃開，快閃開！
我靠！
他死了嗎？
我希望沒有
聽我說，行嗎？
我現在必須要開車出城
不然他們會殺了我妻子
-你明白了嗎？  -當然
聽我一句勸，你下次偷車的時候
先看看裏面有沒有人
-就不會碰到這樣的事了  -我不是偷車賊，這輛車是我的，傻逼
什麼？
你不知道，因為…
你才是偷車賊
這世上每個東西都有自己的主人，但總有人喜歡偷走它
這輛裝著鏡頭、電池、天線…
的車是我的…
那你是怎麼找到這車的？
警察打電話給我，說看到我的車停在一個車庫裏，於是我就找到了你
你怎麼知道他就是警察？
當然是他說的啊，天才
哪個警察會告訴你的車在哪…
卻不帶你一起去？
-他根本不是警察  -那他是誰？
我不知道
-車是什麼時候被偷了？  -你偷的你問我？
最後一次看到這車是什麼時候？
我記得應該是兩天前，你看起來很不對勁
無論你碰到任何麻煩都是你自己的事情，現在我們來作筆交易
靠邊，乖乖滾下車，我就不會報警抓你
不然呢？你要打死我？
把槍給我，我很願意效勞
什麼樣的小孩會像你這樣用槍？
所以如果再碰到你這樣的白癡，我會小心的
這對你來說很好，不是嗎？
你聽不聽得出這是誰的聲音？
-你的朋友要你殺了我？  -這不是我朋友
我不是你以為的容易被綁架的人
喔？是麼？
你跟普通人不一樣，對嗎？
幫我一個忙可以嗎？
閉上你的嘴
你才給我閉嘴！
你在做什麼？
你在犯什麼神經？
真不敢相信你把我的手機扔了出去
-我有很多錢，你知道嗎？  -看得出來
如果你放我走，我可以給你很多錢
我不要錢
那你想要什麼？
我要你閉嘴
我要救我老婆
-他綁架了你妻子？  -對
好吧，我不管你們誰欠誰的
這都不管我的事情
我不想在這死的不明不白
我也想放你出去，但是不行
為什麼？
因為他要我帶著你，因為我必須按他說的做
那你打算怎麼辦？
我不知道
他是誰？
-我不知道  -那你知道些什麼？
不多
不，不，不！
起床！
-閉嘴  -哇！啊！
求求你，別這樣，求求你
閉嘴
我在
你的下一個任務的時間
是什麼呢？
警察追來了
你有4分鐘的時間逃脫
嚴格按照我的指示
有人想跟你打個招呼
求求你，求求你
琳恩？
求求你，救救我
現在開始計時
我靠！
完蛋了
喔！
-加速前衝  -你要幹什麼？
-天啊  -繼續開
你這個白癡，他們
會殺了你的
-加速  -靠
右轉，就是現在
不要忘了
如果你被逮捕…
你的妻子就不保了
-左轉  -我靠
-把他撞開  -小心！
-我簡直不能相信是真的！  -你在說什麼？
你以後最好不要讓我看到你
上帝，我今後一定好好做人，快救救我吧
-你確定不能閉上嘴嗎？  -右轉
非常好
右轉進巷子！
住手！
我靠！
-2分鐘  -我們會死的，快停下來！
我不認為你能成功
你在做什麼？
深呼吸，放鬆點
我靠
如果我是你，我就沒這麼樂觀
-靠  -不要
-你逃脫了嗎？  -不，不要！
天啊！
你的時間不多了
喔！喔！
滴答，滴答
不到一分鐘了
-進入公園  -別進去！
沒事的，我們進去
時間已經快到了
小心！
衝過路口
再堅持一下！
沒有時間了，麥格納先生
天啊！
-不！別這樣！  -堅持就快了！
5…
4…快，快，快啊！
3…
-2…  -喔！
1…
0！
布蘭特·麥格納先生，幹得好！
完美
你的妻子還活著…
現在
幹得好
我在
『布倫特·麥格納是一個魯莽可怕的人』
『是一個，嗯…』
『一個危險的車手，應該盡早換一份工作』
你還記得他嗎？惹人厭的傢伙
他們無視你真正的才華
但我非常看好你
我認識你嗎？
我認識你，麥格納先生…
-而且我願意相信你  -聽我說
你什麼時候才能放我老婆出來？我要…
你在做什麼？
嘿，你打算幹什麼？
-我恨你  -是麼，我愛你
你知道嗎我要重新買一輛謝爾比超級蛇限量版…
再花六個月的時間來改裝
然後我要開著它壓過你的臉
-你很懂機械，雖然你是個…  -是個女孩？
對
哇喔
我喜歡跑車、電腦、很Man的東西
現在是21世紀了，你應該考慮加入我們
-你在做什麼？  -我要錄證據
被捕後我才不要去坐牢
-沒有人會被捕，好嗎？  -喔對，我差點忘了
我們會直接掛掉…
就因為你這個白癡，攻擊警察
現在全國每一個警察都想抓到我們…
在我們的頭上來兩槍
-我們還活著  -勉強活著
你又不是個偉大的思想家？
你知道嗎，其實我還沒有畢業…
所以你或許還能教我點什麼
看看他幹的好事，我帥氣的跑車
快回來坐好
看看我的碳纖維車蓋
這就是那個白癡，讓我陷入了這個爛攤子
-別錄了  -跟法官打個招呼吧
-向你的獄友問個好  -快關掉
你現在又在幹什麼？
-老實點可以嗎？  -為什麼要聽你的？
因為這傢伙在看著我們
-我希望你能安靜一會…  -我知道我在幹什麼
-你能安靜的呆2秒聽我說嗎？  -我知道我在幹什麼
我在學校接受到過教育…
這就是為什麼我不必去偷東西，不像某些人
既然你這麼聰明，能不能告訴我這些相機是怎麼回事
所有相機都連接到同一個端口
沒有加密，但是盜用了政府伺服器
喔？
也就是說
他們能直接使用政府伺服器
可以看到城市裏所有角落
-等等  -怎麼了？
-這些端口不來自同一個地方  -來自於哪裏？
看起來是個地下停車場
-你能獲取具體位置嗎？  -沒辦法，它可能在任何一個地方
-你覺得會在哪裏？  -我不確定
但他可以看到我們，讓我很不爽
您可以追蹤到他嗎？
不行，如果有人試圖追蹤，他就會改變IP地址
只要他用的是伺服器，就有沒有辦法找到它
-但是有其他方法  -什麼？
麥克風
-你還在聽這個？  -或許吧
好我不得不承認，你很聰明
這就是所謂的禮貌
你應該嘗試停止繼續犯罪
如果你繼續這樣，他們會把你送進監獄
我在
看導航儀上的地圖
我現在有點忙
你要學會一心兩用
或者向你的小夥伴尋求幫助
你能把遮陽板放下來嗎？
我發送了一個新的路線圖
發電廠
晚上十一點半
我在那等你
為什麼我們要去發電廠？
既然你誠心誠意的發問了，我就告訴你
因為我喜歡
現在聽我說
我要你到控制室裏
進入遠程伺服器…
-把這個密匙插進去  -你要幹什麼？
你是個聰明的女孩，你一定明白的
他要切斷電源，你為什麼要切斷電源？
還要過一會才到十一點半
如果我是你，我不會浪費時間來瞭解我的動機
他是一個徹底的混蛋
你不知道他是誰
對
-也沒有任何頭緒？  -我有一些猜測
可能是以前和我一起工作的人…
但我知道沒有人會安排這些事情
為什麼他選擇你？
因為我是個優秀的車手
-關於這點還有待商確  -我的意思是在賽車場上
真的假的？
真的
專業，真正的賽車
我不記得我在電視上見過你
是啊，你在那可能有幾個星期了
什麼？
什麼什麼？
我退出了比賽
怎麼個情況？
我也不知道，反正就是退出了，現在說這個沒意義
真是個完美的回答
我退出因為有人誇我有多麼偉大
原來我唯一擅長的就是撞毀昂貴的賽車
我不再比賽後，欠了很多錢
賽車是我唯一擅長的事情…
對此我傾注了很多心血
我贏了很多比賽，但我並不感到光榮
然後我就走了，而這個…
我的妻子
她很漂亮
-她是我們這兒的人？  -對
她一直想回來，我們認為這會是個好地方…
慢慢重新開始生活
我今天下班回家，看到大門開著…
地板上有血跡
然後我接到電話，告訴我說…
如果我想…
如果我想再次見到我的妻子…
我就必須按他們說的做
如果我告訴任何人這事，我妻子就死定了
然後我就開著你的車
你改裝了這輛車？
對，這是我的畢業禮物
調試的很好，也看出你父親不是一個機械師
他是我們這裏最大銀行的CEO
我們大約兩年前搬到這裏
之後就很少看到他
但這輛車是他給我的最好的禮物
很抱歉把你車搞成這樣
你道歉我也不一定就要原諒你
你也可以一槍打爆我的頭
如果你讓我出去的話我會的
現在我只關心一件事…
我會不惜一切代價救我的妻子
所以他說要你留在車上，你就得呆著
為什麼你就得聽他的
為什麼發生這些事？他到底要幹什麼？
你顯然沒有想過這些問題
當這一切結束時會發生什麼事？
為什麼他會讓你妻子回來？
如果我是他，我會殺了你妻子
我靠
怎麼了？
可能也會殺了我
看起來他們已經來過這裏
如果他在這裏，為什麼不自己去切斷電源？
我不知道
停車
怎麼了？
你不知道嗎，金屬的車輛…
靠近變壓器會被電流擊穿的
在這等著，我來處理
等等，什麼？
我要進去
你確定嗎？
我應該把車開出去
不對，我應該開進去
不對，她很清醒，她知道她在做什麼
哈囉？聽得到嗎？我時間緊迫
我與一名男子在車上，他的妻子被綁架
請慢慢說英語
快點派人來，快點！
-情況有多緊急？  -我不知道
有人打電話命令我們按他說的做，你必須幫幫我們
-位置是在哪裏呢？  -我在發電廠
-哈哈哈，你很機靈  -媽的
不管在哪裏都很聰明，我已經去過那裏了
看看你的周圍
看到了嗎？就是那個
警察會認為是你炸毀電廠的
過度充電
我有個建議給你
快跑
快，快啊
-走，走，快走！  -發生什麼事了？
-救命，救命啊！快走！  -發生什麼事了？
堅持一下，媽的
啊！
加速！
快加速！
喔！
你在做什麼？你在做什麼？
我不想因為你去坐牢！
-發生了什麼事？  -這是他的計劃的一部分
我剛才被監控拍下了
他玩弄我們在鼓掌之中…
他在一步步誘導我們
你以為警察現在還會相信我們嗎？
開始這只是你自己的事情…
還把我的車拖下水
現在，我也被牽扯進來了
對不起
我會照顧好我自己
我在
不能讓她走
見鬼去吧
要去哪裡？要去哪裡？等等！
琳恩！琳恩！你能聽到嗎？
聽到嗎？幫幫忙
琳恩，你能聽到我嗎？
布蘭特，這是怎麼回事？
你還好嗎？他們傷害你了嗎？
-這是怎麼回事？  -琳恩！
-救救我！布蘭特  -琳恩！你受傷了，你還好嗎？
快救救我！我好害怕
我馬上就來救你，一切都會結束的，好嗎？
-會結束的  -啊！
什麼…？
放開我老婆！我要看到她！
你們把我老婆怎麼樣了？
我跟你說過不要讓她下車
-我只是想看看…  -我警告過你
對不起
這不是你的錯
我知道我很沒用，但我不能放棄我老婆
她還活著
你沒有義務幫我
我自願的
你在做什麼？
我猜到了他的計劃
我靠
躲下去，快
什麼都沒有
他讓你在路上製造混亂
警察封鎖了很多路口
這些路口一半以上都是單行道
已經無法通行
現在只有一條路可以出城
其他的都走不通
這看起來是一個撤退路線
真想知道他到底要幹什麼
我也是
-我在  -有個好消息
這是你最後一個任務了
查看你的導航
按照這個路線開，你有十分鐘
銀行
哪家銀行？
他想讓我們搶我父親的銀行
我靠！
我們不會去的
計時已經開始了
我們兩個人怎麼可能搶的了銀行
不要在意這些細節
-他就是想要我們被抓住  -注意看導航，掉頭
這等於是自殺，我們不能去
別理她，聽我指令，掉頭
我要確定我妻子沒事
快掉頭
我耐心有限
我們好好商量可以嗎？
沒的商量
我什麼時候才能看到我老婆
聽我的指令
我最後一次警告你
我要看到她沒事
什麼時候才能結束這一切
你是不想再見到你妻子了嗎？
把車開過去
你別聽他的
-聽我說！這是一個陷阱！  -他們會殺了我老婆
你知道為什麼他們要用我的車嗎？
仔細想想吧
我爸斷了我的生活費
現在我的車在城裏亂竄
然後所有人都看到我搶劫了銀行？
他就是想讓我當替罪羊
-他想要的是什麼？  -當然是錢
這就是問題所在，它不是那種銀行
什麼意思？
我爸爸那是一家投資銀行
-根本沒有現金可以搶  -我靠！
-天啊  -你是什麼意思，那只有保險櫃？
也沒有保險櫃，那兒只有一堆電腦
-債券呢？不記名債券  -債券？現在什麼年代了？
那他到底要幹嘛？
他要偷的是什麼？
除非…
坐穩！
除非什麼？
除非你有一筆黑錢
-洗黑錢？  -沒錯
-怎麼才能洗乾淨黑錢呢？  -小心，小心！
-快說說  -銀行對賬戶數據進行加密的…
有一個數據傳輸密鑰
如果能拿到這個密鑰呢…？
-就可以使用那個賬戶  -對
沒人會發現有錢被動過，賬戶根本就不存在
-會有多少錢？  -可能會有數十億美元
我應該也去開個銀行
你不會真的要
我靠！
-我會盡力的  -別，別這樣
嘿餵狗！
我靠好險
啊！
啊！滾開！
小心！
我恨你一個洞
我曉得
-你在做什麼？  -別廢話！
好，我們保持冷靜，安靜的坐一會
打完收工，我們贏得了一點時間
什麼意思？
我進入伺服器，把剛才錄的一段視頻循環播放
-這樣他就暫時只能看到這個視頻  -幹嘛這樣？
現在聽我說
當我們到銀行後，我們會被抓住，他會殺了你妻子
我們是他的誘餌
-非常好  -現在切斷了電源…
銀行的安全系統就失效了
當發生這種情況，會啟動一個應急機制
我靠
我父親曾經提到過這個的
轉移，現在正在轉移
把重要的數據轉移到一個安全的地方…
…直到系統恢復正常
等我們到達銀行的時候…
只有一個空蕩蕩的銀行
現在我們要找個地方靜觀其變
我保證銀行周圍全都是警察
我們有多少時間？
五到十分鐘
看你能去哪裡，混蛋！
我去看看
怎麼樣了？
很糟糕
現在該怎麼辦？
我正在想
你之前說如果電力中斷他們就會
轉移數據？
對
轉去哪裏？
我不知道，這是銀行的機密
我靠
但是他們要過去拿對不對，他們已經快得手了
而所有警察都在這裏
這兒有後門或其他入口嗎？
記得那個停車場嗎？
你覺得他會在那裏嗎？
有可能
我敢打賭，他就在那裏
你可能是對的
我們走
接入碼
3，1…
9，7，2…
1，3，4…
2，6…
什麼？
快，快，快！
-好了  -走吧！
快追上去！
接電話
接電話，接電話
給我接電話！
我在
你死定了，你老婆完了，遊戲結束！
現在我們佔上風，混蛋！
你可以開穩一點嗎？
等我拔出密鑰？
到手了！
撞他！撞他！
你妹的！
我靠！
天啊，快走！
趴下！趴下！
快離開這鬼地方
喔！
小心！
坐穩！
索非亞警方
我靠
靠邊停車！
放棄抵抗
車裏的人，立刻靠邊停車
我們被困住了，準備好了了嗎？
槍？槍呢？
-把槍給我！  -你已經被包圍了
好了跟我來，走
別過來！
不然我打爆她的頭！
退後！沒看到嗎？
退後，我會殺了她的
我會殺了她的
我要打爆她的頭！
嘿！你！你！對就是你！
你還好嗎？
都退後，我會殺了她的？
退後！
對很好，就這樣
快閃開，條子們
真不敢相信這是我幹的
他們還沒被捕，我把位置給你
抓住他們
怎麼了？
你快離開這
什麼？
你不再有嫌疑
他們會認為你是被我綁架的
-不，我…  -我說真的
你已經盡力了
我不能再讓你冒生命危險
-你必須離開這  -不行
-下車  -不
走吧，你快走吧
我要跟你一起去
你真是個固執的人？
我知道
我不會離開我的車
如果我不在你要打算怎麼辦
好吧
你還不知道我叫什麼名字吧？
不知道
喔！快走！
我靠！
-哇！  -你沒事吧？
撞他！
趴下！
趴好！
小心！
天啊
要掉下去了！
-槍在哪裏？  -我不知道！
-槍在哪裏？  -我在找！
快找槍！
-找到了嗎？快給我  -在這在這兒呢
幫我扶一下方向盤！
幫我掛到低檔，準備好了嗎？
快！
我有一個想法
下車
我們去找他
我們用數據換你的妻子
他不會答應的，他會把我們都殺了
我有一個辦法
在車前架設鏡頭，把畫面發給警方
警察會明白一切
接電話
-我在  -你覺得你很
-聰明是不是…  -不，閉嘴
我們有你想要的，我要見你
在哪裏？
在我上班的地方
給你兩小時到那
晚安，混蛋
我老婆在哪？
我的密鑰呢？
我老婆在哪兒？
不，不！不！
琳恩！
布蘭特？
我要確定這是真的密鑰
你
跟著他！
先放了他老婆
天啊，你終於來了
我愛你
怎麼樣
稍等
我們該走了
殺了他們！
布蘭特！小心！
不！不！
-抓住她！  -不！啊！
-你還好嗎？  -我沒事
靠，他們抓走了那女孩
-我要去救她  -快去
你和警察呆在一起
你慢點！
你受傷了嗎？
靠
他有槍
快來救我
聽見了沒
-你能看見這個平板嗎  -噓！
別說話
布蘭特，我把位置發給你
別擋路！
布蘭特，你在哪！
-你真他媽是混蛋！  -你閉嘴！
來吧，我們來玩吧
啊！
我靠！
你在幹什麼？在錄影？
拿來！快給我！
媽的！
我靠！
靠
這是唯一一條撤退的路
我知道了
-把槍給我！  -你幹什麼，老實點！
你死定了？
布蘭特，快，快點！
-滾下車！  -什麼？
滾下車！
沒事吧？
你還好嗎？
你被捕了
謝謝
全部後退！
嗚！
-我欠你一個人情  是吧？  -你欠我一輛新車
別擔心，它只是需要一個修理工
-什麼聲音？  -不知道
不是我的手機
-喂  -不用謝我
我幫你做到你做不到的事
我看到了你的表現
請原諒我
不能親自到場
我有點不方便…
你一定想知道他們是誰…
他們都是你狂熱的崇拜者
我一直認為你可以在自己的領域獨領風騷…
只要你相信自己
你看，你做到了
請允許我對你的妻子致以最誠摯的祝福
我很喜歡她為你準備的聖誕節禮物
多點時間陪陪自己的家人
我沒有什麼親人
唯一能安慰我的就是我有很多錢
而現在我看到了你，非常感謝
我們以後還會有交集的
所以，現在還是先說一句
再見
我向你保證…
以後會更加有意思的
字
字幕
字幕製
字幕製作
字幕製作 ★
字幕製作 ★ 至
字幕製作 ★ 至宏
字幕製作 ★ 至宏上
字幕製作 ★ 至宏上人